(Sheldon:)I was promised a riverboat journey
into the jungles of my subconscious.
(Sheldon:)Instead I get the same question...
(Sheldon:)...I hear from the lady
who slices my bologna at Ralph's.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry. I'll start again.
(Sheldon:)Would it be helpful to you
if I told you about my dreams?
(Leonard:)Um.... I don't know, maybe.
(Sheldon:)I recently had a dream
that I was a giant.
(Sheldon:)But everything around me
was to scale so it all looked normal.
Well, how did you know you were
a giant if everything was to scale?
(Sheldon:)I was wearing size a million pants.
(Leonard:)-Why don't we just talk?
-Ah. The talking cure.
(Sheldon:)Classical Freudian. Good choice.
(Sheldon:)If it will help speed things along...
(Sheldon:)...my answers to the standard
Rorschach inkblot test are:
(Sheldon:)A, a bat, B, a bat, C, a bat...
(Sheldon:)...and D, my father killing my mother
with a hypodermic needle.